I remind you of the importance of understanding that by being this base around the second
我还是要提醒你们，理解这一点的重要性，在第二周左右，作为这个基础，
week,
周，
I have this S-shape of my epiblastic process
我的外胚层过程呈S形
which will form the notochord
它将形成脊索
and finally Hensen's node, the primitive streak which
最终是亨森氏结，原始凹陷，它
will be here, becomes a fulcrum
将在这里，成为一个支点
and will become a fixed point.
并将成为一个固定点。
And then this Hensen's node will gradually move backwards.
然后这个亨森氏结会一点一点地向后移动。
there is a unity
有一个统一性
finally, because this will form
最终，因为这会形成
what? It will form the base of my skull
什么？它会形成我的颅底
you see
你明白吗
with my energy
带着我的能量
the chi, the pituitary gland which will be
气，垂体将会在
there, with the
那里，伴随着
process of the greater wings of the sphenoid
蝶骨大翼的过程
the petrous system
岩骨系统
and the occipital system
和枕骨系统
and my ethmoid
和我的筛骨
you see, here what will happen
你看，这里会发生什么
well my notochord
我的脊索
and below what will I
下面我会
I will have the development of my sacrum.
我将会有骶骨的发育。
At the level of S2,
在S2水平，
and then it will be the vestige of my primitive line.
然后这将是我原始线的遗迹。
So, this process here becomes a fulcrum,
所以，这个过程在这里成为一个支点，
that's why to free this process here,
这就是为什么为了释放这个过程，
there, I must have a free sacrum,
我必须有一个自由的骶骨，
because it is a functional unit.
因为它是一个功能单元。
In this phase of development,
在这个发展阶段，
the embryo will have this somewhat...
胚胎会呈现出这种有点像...
racket shape with my notochord and my primitive streak, there is in this process
球拍的形状，我的脊索和我的原始线，在这个过程中
of growth a
的生长有一个
field of aspiration to form the mesoderm.
吸引场来形成中胚层。
Already, the precardiac field and all the mesoderm,
已经，心前区和所有中胚层，
we will say intermediate, which will be pulled
我们可以说是中间的，它将被拉动
by the anterior growth of
通过胚胎的前部生长，它将吸入所有物质。
the embryo which will aspirate all the material.
胚胎将吸入所有物质。
in this area, you see,
在这个区域，你看，
where there will be cells in the shape
那里会有细胞形成
of bottle cells which are
瓶状细胞被
aspirated towards the center, you see,
吸向中心，你明白吗？
and which will release an acid,
它们会释放一种酸，
hyaluronic acid,
即透明质酸，
which is primary at the mesenchymal level.
它在间充质层面是原发的。
It's really a level
这确实是一个
important that is done by
重要的层面，通过
the growth process.
生长过程实现。
So it's the growth that pulls
所以是生长牵引着
the information. So the importance
信息。因此，脊索轴的
of this notochordal axis,
重要性，
the importance of this center
这个中心的重要性，
importance of having a free sacrum. If your sacrum is not free, your spine cannot
拥有一个自由的骶骨的重要性。如果你的骶骨不自由，你的脊柱就
be
无法
free. If your spine cannot be free, the base of your skull cannot
自由。如果你的脊柱无法自由，你的颅底就无法
be free. If the base of your skull is not free, you cannot have good flexion
自由。如果你的颅底不自由，你就无法拥有良好的屈伸。
extension. That is to say, you cannot have a balance between your neurocranium
也就是说，你无法在你的神经颅和
and your viscerocranium. That's what I explained earlier. It's this
内脏颅之间取得平衡。这就是我刚才解释的。
It's this
这是
ascending force of the skull in which the eye will settle.
颅骨上升的力量，眼睛将在此处安放。
establishment of this third tissue,
这第三种组织，
mesodermal tissue,
中胚层组织，的形成，
with the ectodermal growth that pulls,
伴随着外胚层生长的牵引，
the regression more or less, let's say, of the primitive node
原始结的退化，大约，可以说，
which descends, you see,
它下降，你明白吗？
down to the level of the sacrum.
直到骶骨的水平。
And so it becomes a very important area
因此，这成为一个非常重要的区域，
in protein information vis-à-vis the mother.
在蛋白质信息方面，相对于母亲。
That's why many ancestral images that are blocked
这就是为什么许多被阻塞的祖先形象
are located between the sigmoid and the bladder.
位于乙状结肠和膀胱之间。
That's where you will block the images received from the mother.
你会在那里阻塞从母亲那里接收到的形象。
That's where you have to go and clear them.
你必须去那里解除它们。
All urogenital problems, like that, transmitted by these informations.
所有泌尿生殖系统的问题，都是通过这些信息传递的。
And then this downward sacral migration force, as I explained earlier, at
然后是骶骨向下迁移的力量，就像我刚才解释的，在
that level.
这个层面上。